Wanted Outlaw Posters Collection, 1911-1915: Finding Aid
Princeton University Library. Department of Rare Books and Special Collections.
Wanted Outlaws Posters Collection
1911-1915
WC127
Princeton University. Library. Department of Rare Books and Special Collections One Washington Road Princeton, New Jersey 08544 USA
1.5 linear feet 1 box
Princeton University. Library. Dept. of Rare Books and Special Collections.
The Wanted Outlaws Posters Collection contains 10 wanted posters for horse theft, larceny, counterfeiting, and murder from Colorado, Idaho, Montana, South Dakota, Utah, and Wyoming.
This collection contains 10 wanted posters for horse theft, larceny, counterfeiting, and murder from Colorado, Idaho, Montana, South Dakota, Utah, and Wyoming. According to records, all but Frank De Challis were eventually captured.
Collection is open for research use.
Digital images of the collection are available at: http://libweb.princeton.edu/libraries/firestone/rbsc/aids/WC127/.
Outlaws -- West (U.S.) -- History -- 20th century -- Sources.; Posters -- West (U.S.); Western Americana
- B. Berger, alias Leo Botrick, Salt Lake City, Utah, 1915 July 31; 1; 1 item (Box 1)
  Wanted for grand larceny.
- Chester Cantrel, Wibaux County, Montana, 1915; 2; 1 item (Box 1)
  Wanted for theft of blue serge suit.
- Frank De Challis, Digarris, Denver, Colorado, undated; 3; 1 item (Box 1)
  Wanted for counterfeit money and jumping bond.
- Clifford Hunt, attached to Clyde Douglas, Fort Collins, Colorado, 1915 January; 4; 1 item (Box 1)
  Both wanted for horse stealing
- Mel B. Jowell, also known as Mal Louell, Big Timber, Montana, 1911 November; 5; 1 item (Box 1)
  Wanted for murder.
- W. W. McCracken, Belle Fourche, South Dakota, 1913 August; 6; 1 item (Box 1)
  Wanted for larceny of horses.
- John McGuire, Davis County, Utah, 1915 July; 7; 1 item (Box 1)
  Escaped from Convict Camp.
- J. C. D. Pratt, Bannock County, Idaho, 1912 December; 8; 1 item (Box 1)
  Wanted for felony, embezzlement and horse stealing.
- Noah T. Richardson, J. H. Burke, and E. Baxtrum, Rawlins, Wyoming, 1912 October; 9; 1 item (Box 1)
  Escaped convicts.
- Joe M. Romo, Dillon, Montana, 1915 April; 10; 1 item (Box 1)
  Wanted for murder, ms. note sighting on notice.